What is the
fu... What is the fu...
What is the future...
What is the fu...
What is the future?
Theme song playing
What is the future...
- News! Bad!
We're bankrupt.
Oh, I borrowed money
to invest in Bitcoin.
Then the price crashed,
and I sold at a huge loss.
We're ruined!
Oh, sorry. I didn't realize
you were watching TV.
- The tragic impact
destroyed the planet Klarg,
along with its 50
billion inhabitants.
- In other news, Morbo,
guess what's back?
- The planet Klarg?
- Nope!
The price of Bitcoin!
- Uh, wha?!
- The virtual "money"
is soaring once again,
leading to a
high-tech gold rush.
- Prospectors are heading
west, where cheap,
filthy electricity
beckons the desperate.
- This gives me
a desperate idea!
- Haven't you
learned that Bitcoin
is just a pyramid
scheme for rubes?
- Yes, and my plan
is to exploit those rubes!
You see, the new mining chips
are made from element 81,
thallium, a rare
element found out west.
I plan to actually mine it,
then sell it to the
Bitcoin "miners."
It's a sure way to
repay my loan brokers.
- Yo. We're also leg brokers.
- Goodbye, Robot Mafia!
- The Bitcoin mines are using
such colossal amounts of power
that it's ionizing
the atmosphere.
We'll need to land and
drive the rest of the way.
- I'll set her down
on the Donner trail.
It's a good thing we brought
the oxen. Usually, we don't.
- I've never been
out west before,
but I'm learning a lot from
these Borax Kid action books.
I'm
robbing this vault
and ain't no ionic
compound gonna stop me!
Freeze, Maxwell's Demon.
I'd advise you to drop
those gold molecules.
The Borax Kid!
I'm gonna pump you full of lead.
- You know, 'round these parts,
folks don't think things.
They reckon them. And
instead of an idiot,
I'll be known as a galoot!
- Isn't this scenery spectacular, Dwight?
- Uh-huh.
Your mother thought you'd
enjoy some fresh air for once.
She sure was wrong.
- Well, anyway, I'm
really looking forward
to some quality father-son time.
- With who?
- Ah, crypto country.
There's thallium
in them thar hills!
Priceless, toxic thallium.
- Um, is this thallium?
- Oh my, yes! High-grade ore!
- Um, Professor? Toxic.
- Relax. They're my
prospecting teeth.
Oh, quit your
chattering. We're almost there.
- Welcome to Doge City!
Looks like you got seven
hornswogglers and a galoot!
- Woo-hoo! We made it!
- It's pretty lawless out
here in crypto country,
so put on your
protective headgear.
Hiya!
- Kind of old-fashioned for a town
built on high-speed computation.
- Well, every watt
of electricity
goes to the Bitcoin
mining computers.
For everyone else,
it's practically like
living in the Old West.
- Old West. Got it.
- Until we stake our
claim and strike it rich,
keep in mind, we're bankrupt.
So we'll all need to do
Old West stuff to get by.
- Old West. Got it.
- Welcome, friends.
What'll you have?
- Your freest beverage.
We're very poor.
- Gotcha. I'll just mix all the unfinished
drinks together and start a tab.
- She seems nice.
- At times, yes.
Though her mood fluctuates
like the price of Bitcoin.
- And don't come back
till you settle your tab!
Though, I do regret hurting
you. I tell you what.
Go see the girls in the
back room. It's on me.
- Girls?
- Yep.
Delilah runs a house
of ill repute in back.
- "Ill"? You mean a hospital?
- I mean a cathouse.
- A pet store?
- A brothel.
- A soup kitchen?!
- Yeah. A soup kitchen.
- Whoa! Who's that?
- A psychotic killer,
that's who! Get down!
- Hey, Roberto!
What's with the piece?
I thought you were
more of a knife guy.
- Out here in the West, I
need something shootier.
Like this gun-knife
I invented-stole!
Where's that beer I
ordered-didn't order?!
You didn't order a...
- Say, you're new in
town and low on cash.
You interested in a job as a
barmaid and/or a prostitute?
- Um, I'm not sure Leela has
the skills to be a barmaid.
- Gimme the tray!
- Alright, up next,
our final item.
This burro is in
near-mint condition.
Perfect for hauling Bitcoin,
light housework, or just abusing.
Bidders? Bidders? Do
I have any bidders?
- Twelve-millionths
of a Bitcoin!
- Twelve micro-Bitcoin. Do
I hear 13? Thirteen, 13?
- Not from me, you don't!
- Fifteen! I always
wanted to own a racehorse.
- That's a donkey, Bender.
- Donkeys are just
ugly horses, Amy.
Sold to the zoologist over there!
- Oh! I'm gonna call him Rusty.
- Good 'cause that's his name!
- Ah! This looks like a
good place to make camp.
Doesn't it look like a
good place to make camp?
- It looks stupid. This
whole trip is stupid.
You're stupid, Pops!
- I appreciate your
constructive criticism, son.
- I wish Roberto were my dad.
He's cooler than a green snake
smoking a sugar cane vape.
- No self-respecting
green snake would do that!
Kind sir, could you assay this nugget?
By my tooth test, I
estimate it's 0.3% thallium.
- Tooth test?
- Balderweeds.
Let's see what my
metallurgical analyzer says.
0.3% thallium.
- Hoo-hoo, boy!
I'll give you 100
micro-Bitcoin for it.
- But weed a million times that
amount or we're gonna get clamped!
Robot
Mafia, huh? Eh.
Well, maybe there's some thallium
in that there chassis of yours.
- Assay my shiny metal ass!
0.0000...
- Tain't even
worth melting down.
- Well then, perhaps my ass
might be of value to you
in some other way?
- Eh, it might make
a good frying pan,
but fried food makes
me cackle.
- We'll just sell
you the nugget.
May I ask who turns the
thallium into microchips?
- I'm an all-in-one operation.
My motto is, "He who
smelts it, dealts it!"
Pop one of those in a
high-end server, and blam!
You're mining crypto.
Ooh, lookie there!
Found another Bitcoin!
Aw, dog dumplings.
It's just a danged Ethereum.
- Hello, I'm Zoidberg.
Like you, I'm a doctor.
So, uh, what's
your survival rate?
- Pretty high. I'm
a psychiatrist.
Got a patient coming 'round
for anger management about now.
- Hiya, Doc. Boy, it's
been a stressful week.
What's with the jumbo prawn?
- A colleague.
Mind if he sits in?
- Yes, I do mind!
I value doctor-patient
confidentiality!
Patang! DOCTOR: Ah!
- So, how's business?
- Disappointing. I only
got 30 cents in tips
and one request to
visit the back room.
I mean, I wouldn't go,
but it's nice to be asked.
Can you think of anything
I can do to look sluttier?
Nope.
Look! The Borax Kid!
And his sidekick Mumbles!
- You know he's not actually a
hero like in his books, right?
He's a poker cheat and
a low-down base mineral.
- Wow. The Borax Kid.
Excuse me, Mr. Kid.
My name is Fry, and I'm a big fan
of your young adult adventures.
- Oh, really? Uh,
do you play poker?
- Yeah, but I was warned
not to play poker with you.
- Well, then how about a
hand of Colorado Chump?
- As long as it's not poker.
So what are you doing here?
Fighting evil or just
helping townspeople?
- Not much money
in helping folks.
Double chump. You lose.
I heard the
Borax Kid's in town.
Come on out here, Kid!
- Mumbles, go see what
all that fuss is about.
And wear my signature hat.
Pa-pow-pow!
- Mumbles is dead!
Don't argue with me,
Mumbles. I'm the town doctor.
- Well, shucks. My sidekicks
seem to be dying right regular.
And in gruesome fashion.
Care to be my new sidekick?
- Really? Do I get to
die in your next book?
- Page three.
- Then you got
yourself a galoot.
- Nice camp. Is this my tent?
- No. You only
come in to tidy up.
There's just enough room for me
and my private library there.
- Can I sleep in the library?
- I'd like to say yes, but
then it wouldn't be private.
- This place has
too much outdoors!
It's all bugs and no Wi-Fi.
- Don't get your
dreads in a knot, son.
Any more than they're
supposed to be.
How about a father-son
limbo break?
- I hate limbo, Dad!
Limbo is stupid.
- Limbo stupid?
Where did I go wrong?
- Probably when
you took up limbo.
From what I'm
hearing, it's stupid.
- Bender! Where are the
shovels I asked you to pack?
- Oh, you said shovels?
I thought you said take
a break and do nothing.
- Hm. Then we'll just
have to find thallium
the old-fashioned
way. By panning.
- Panning? With what?
Sometimes, I
think a detachable ass
is more a curse than a
blessing. Come on, Rusty.
We're just a guy with no ass
And his ass
Assin' it up under
an asinine sky
Assin' to the
tumbleweeds as we ass by
Yodeling a cowboy tune
But, not yet!
People sass me on
my ass as we pass
They say, wouldn't it be
better if my ass rode me?
They tell me I
outweigh my ass
By a factor of three
So, I punch 'em
and I kick their
Yodel-odel-ay-hee-hoo
harmonizing braying
Ass, butt, rear-end, ass
Yodel-ay hee hoo...
- What the? Rusty!
- No!
Oh, why didn't I
listen to my own song?!
- Get yourself tuned or get outta
town, you overgrowed teletype machine.
- Eh, shut your cackling trap!
- Cram that racket!
This is a nice, quiet saloon
with attached bordello.
- You handle the
menfolk pretty well.
But mess with my
customers again,
and I'll kill you in your sleep!
Lovin' the boots.
- Um, have you
considered seeing someone
about your mood swings?
- No!
But it is a good idea.
Mr. Roberto?
Folks call me Amarillo Dwight.
On account of I wrote a
geography report on it.
Done got me a "A."
How's about you and me
team up and rob stuff?
- What are you, like, 11?
- Twelve.
- Close enough. I need a
kid for a job I'm planning.
See that stagecoach?
It's taking a USB stick
with a company's weekly
haul of Bitcoin credentials
to a bank in San Francisc-y.
Only, they ain't never
gonna reach San Francisc-y.
- Why not? They
using Apple Maps?
Not one patient.
Not even a case of splinters
to treat with my bone saw.
Thanks, robot, but I couldn't
eat a thing right now.
Can
you save him, Doc?
- If it's something that
can be cured by a bone saw!
I'll need anesthetic!
Get me a bottle
of animal whiskey!
Ha-ha!
They see a cute kid
lying in the road,
stagecoach gotta stop.
Then I jump out and stab 'em!
Bang!
- But, won't that
be, like, murder?
'Cause colleges look
at stuff like that.
- Here they come!
Shut up and look cute.
Guess you ain't as
cute as I thought.
- The West can be
dangerous at night, Leela,
so thanks for walking me home.
Don't worry. The Kid will save
us, right? - Right.
Better back off, puma.
- I think it's
actually a cougar.
- Puma, cougar,
whatever! Get him, Kid!
- Or a mountain lion. You know,
they're really all the same animal.
- It seems I bravely
shot that catamount
just in time after Fry missed.
- Thanks, Kid. Maybe
I was wrong about you.
- Beautiful ladies are
wrong about lots of things.
- Ah, it's nice to see you two
getting along so intimately.
- It's hopeless!
There's barely any thallium!
Just worthless gold.
- Well, Rusty's good as new!
- I performed surgery
on Bender's ass!
Zoidberg is the hero!
- No! Bender's ass is!
- I mean his butt ass.
- It's so beautiful.
Hey, what's that big rock on it?
- It's enough thallium
to pay off all our debts!
Eh, well, mine, anyway.
- Only the assay shop's
closed for the night,
and it's getting dark.
- We'll have to take
turns guarding the nugget
with our lives until morning.
I'd take a shift myself,
but I am already in my pajamas.
- I steal it. I steal
it not. I steal it...
- Gimme the nugget!
And the daisy, too. I gotta
know how it comes out!
- Ah, nature.
I hate it. Let's sell that
thallium nugget and hit the trail.
- Oh, no. The nugget is gone!
And so is Bender.
Eh, wha?
Oh, my gosh! Rusty!
Bray us what happened!
Come on! He's picked
up Bender's scent!
- His what now?
- Back room don't open
till church lets out.
It's empty!
- This is the worst
brothel I've ever seen.
- It's an immense Bitcoin mine!
Or an even worse brothel.
- These aren't servers.
They're robot heads!
Someone's using them
to mine Bitcoin!
- That's actually a pretty reasonable
use case for robot heads. But...
- Hey! It's a guy I know.
Are you okay, Bender?
- No, I'm not okay!
That's a stupid question!
- I was peacefully
stealing your thallium,
when, suddenly... Ha-ha!
I was kidnapped by our
friend from the saloon.
I'm not your friend.
Though, I
do like you a lot.
- Didn't you ever wonder
who was gettin' rich
off all this Bitcoin nonsense?
- Never!
- Computer servers are expensive,
but robot heads are
cheap. Heck, free.
- Mining Bitcoin with
kidnapped robot heads?
It's pure evil!
- Hardly. I donate all the
proceeds to a local orphanage.
Aw...
- But I can't let you tell
anyone about my generous scheme,
so I'll have to seal you
in this comfortably
air-conditioned warehouse.
Forever!
But I'll drop by
every day with snacks.
Aw... ZOIDBERG:
Snacks are good.
- Huh.
- Crypto mining was total hell.
Any number you can think of,
there's a number bigger
than that!
- So how do we get out of here?
- Easy. We'll burrow out!
Burrow! Burrow!
I deserved that.
- This tie pin?
Why, it was a gift
from my good friend
Diamond Jim Diamond.
- That guy who's just a
big diamond? You know him?
- Step away from Leela, Kid.
The jig is up! I
found your collection
of Buffalo Bill Cobalt novels.
You just copied those and
replaced his name with yours!
- What?!
- Well, now,
there's nothing
illegal about that.
Those old stories
are public domain.
I change up a few words and
claim the copyright for myself.
Ya ever heard of Cinderella?
- That is so evil!
- I'm calling you out, Kid.
I told you, stop
that racket!
- Not till you stop
that damn cackling!
- Then I'm callin' you out.
Delilah,
you head-napper!
I'm calling you out!
You're on.
- Look out, Fry! He's
got the ace of spades!
- That, sir, was
my cheatin' hand.
- Pops! Get outta there!
- I'm too scared! There's
bullets in every dimension!
- Hang on! I'm limboing in!
You. Play something Jamaican.
- Your spine!
It's magnificent!
- I take after my dad.
Also, I got run
over. Now, follow me!
- This gun violence has to end!
Can't we all just
agree to use knives?
Ha-ha!
- Well, shucks.
- Ow!
- Oops. Sorry, Leela.
- Ma'am, I'd be right honored
to disinfect your wound
with the kiss of borax.
May I escort you to the
brothel, so as you can lie down?
- I've never been so offended
yet slightly flattered!
- Then, I reckon
I'll be moseying off
to plagiarize another
adventure. Ma'am.
- Perhaps I could
disinfect your wound.
- I'd like that. Care to
escort me to the brothel?
- It seems, Miss Delilah, you've
taken a shot to the bustle.
- Fortunately, it bounced off
your damned thallium nugget.
Here. It's rightfully yours.
Oh!
Well, I'd better
go exchange this
for Bitcoin, so I can...
Pay back the Robot Mafia?!
- Exactly. I'll be
back in a moment.
- And in the meantime,
how would you gents fancy
a visit to the back room?
That sounds like
something we would enjoy.
- I love you, Pops.
And limbo is not
entirely stupid.
- Oh, son. Neither are you.
- If we ever get outta here,
I'm gonna give this brothel
a really bad Yelp review.